{"message": "Successfully uploaded", "questions": [{"explanation": "to is to", "question": "Select appropiate to from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him _____________ the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["<built-in method lower of str object at 0x105b2cd00>", "to", "<built-in method lower of str object at 0x10bf95c38>", "<built-in method lower of str object at 0x105b2cd78>"]}, {"explanation": "in is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After that they went _____________ search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["<built-in method lower of str object at 0x105d45ae0>", "<built-in method lower of str object at 0x102060e10>", "in", "on"]}, {"explanation": "a is Determiner", "question": "Select appropiate Determiner from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to _____________ tree .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["<built-in method lower of str object at 0x101e6ac10>", "<built-in method lower of str object at 0x101e6ac60>", "a", "<built-in method lower of str object at 0x1020c3f90>"]}, {"explanation": "of is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea _____________ the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["of", "in", "<built-in method lower of str object at 0x105d45ae0>", "<built-in method lower of str object at 0x1020c3b10>"]}, {"explanation": "a is Determiner", "question": "Select appropiate Determiner from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , _____________ few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["<built-in method lower of str object at 0x101e4cd28>", "the", "<built-in method lower of str object at 0x105d13690>", "a"]}, {"explanation": "zoo is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the _____________ .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["<built-in method lower of str object at 0x102080180>", "<built-in method lower of str object at 0x102052450>", "zoo", "<built-in method lower of str object at 0x1020b52a0>"]}, {"explanation": "After is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": " _____________ that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["After", "<built-in method lower of str object at 0x101e4cc88>", "of", "<built-in method lower of str object at 0x10c16d6f0>"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: the", "question": "In the following sentence identify Determiner.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["help", "to", "the", "idea"]}, {"explanation": "and is Coordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Coordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , _____________ tied him to a tree .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["<built-in method lower of str object at 0x105b2cda0>", "and", "<built-in method lower of str object at 0x10bf95c10>", "but"]}, {"explanation": "let is Verb (base form)", "question": "Select appropiate Verb (base form) from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and _____________ him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["let", "<built-in method lower of str object at 0x1020c32a0>", "<built-in method lower of str object at 0x10c16d8d0>", "<built-in method lower of str object at 0x10c16d5d0>"]}, {"explanation": "lifted is Verb (past tense)", "question": "Select appropiate Verb (past tense) from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he _____________ his paw and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["placed", "served", "lifted", "<built-in method lower of str object at 0x105d0dc90>"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: and", "question": "In the following sentence identify Coordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["help", "to", "tickled", "and"]}, {"explanation": "to is to", "question": "Select appropiate to from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , _____________ take him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["to", "<built-in method lower of str object at 0x101e6ac88>", "<built-in method lower of str object at 0x105b2cd78>", "<built-in method lower of str object at 0x105b2cd00>"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: hunters", "question": "In the following sentence identify Pural Noun.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["hunters", "to", "a", "a"]}, {"explanation": "tree is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a _____________ .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["<built-in method lower of str object at 0x1020238d0>", "<built-in method lower of str object at 0x105d2d5a0>", "<built-in method lower of str object at 0x102023030>", "tree"]}], "success": 1}